<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hilsha">
        <u> Ingredients:</u>
\n1. Hilsa (Ilish Mach): 4 pieces
\n2. Eddoe(Mukhi Kochu): 2: peeled and cubed.
\n3. Green Chilies: 4-5, slit longitudinally(according to heat preferences)
\n4. Turmeric: 1-2 tsp
\n5. Red Chili Powder: 1 tsp
\n6. Salt
\n7. Sugar: 1/4 tsp
\n8. Kalo Jeere/Kalonji/Nigella Seeds: 1/2 tsp
\n9. Mustard oil: 6-7 tbsp \n
        <u>Method: </u>
        \n" Clean the fish well, and remove all the scales. Wash it well, under running water, and then pat it dry with a paper towel. Coat the fish pieces with turmeric and some salt. Keep aside.
           Heat mustard oil in a non stick pan. Don't substitute mustard oil, with any other oil, as it lends to the signature taste. So when you buy Ilish Mach, ensure you also have Mustard Oil with you, on stock. Once the oil has just about started to smoke, carefully place the fishes in the pan, and shallow fry them, on moderately high heat. Ilish Mach tends to splutter, so keep a splutter guard handy. Turn the fishes after about frying them for 3 minutes per side, so that they are evenly fried on both sides.
           Remove the fishes from the oil, and add in the diced Mukhi Kochu. Fry them lightly and then keep aside. In the same oil, add in Kalo jeere and the slit green chilies. Let them splutter.
           Meanwhile, make a paste of red chili powder, turmeric powder, salt, sugar and around half a cup of water, in a bowl. Once you get the aroma of green chilies, from the oil, add this spice mixture. Mix well. Add in the fried Kochu, and cover and cook at about medium heat, till the Kochu is almost cooked.
           Add in the fried Ilish Mach carefully in the gravy, and cook uncovered till the Kochu is totally cooked, and the fish has soaked up the gravy well. Reduce the gravy, so that it not too watery, but not too thick.
           Check for seasonings ! Remove from Fire. Serve hot with some steamed Basmati Rice."

    </string>
</resources>