<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="murighon">
        <u> INGREDIENTS: </u>
\n 1.	Rice: 1 cup
\n 2.	Fish head: 1 (medium)
\n 3.	Onions: 2 (medium; finely chopped)
\n 4.	Potatoes: 2 (medium; cut in halves)
\n 5.	Green chillies: 5/6 (chopped)
\n 6.	Ginger paste: 1 tsp
\n 7.	Garlic paste: 1 tsp
\n 8.	Bay leaves: 1-2 (depending on the size)
\n 9.	Dried red chilli: 5-6
\n10.	Cumin seeds: 1 tsp
\n11.	Cinnamon stick: 1”
\n12.	Turmeric powder: 1 +1 tsp
\n13.	Red chilli powder: 1 +1 tsp
\n14.	Cumin powder: 1 tsp
\n15.	Coriander powder: 1 tsp
\n16.	Garam masala powder: 1 tsp
\n17.	Ghee: 1 tbsp
\n18.	Water: 2 cups
\n19.	Sugar
\n20.	Salt to taste
      \n  <u>PREPARATION:</u>
          \n Wash and clean the rice and keep aside. If you are using basmati soak it in enough water for 1 hour. For ‘Govindo Bhog’ rice you don’t need do this.
             Clean the fish head carefully. Sprinkle and rub some salt and turmeric and red chilli powder and leave it for 20 mins.
             Fry the fish head until it turns golden brown. Try to break them into small pieces to avoid mess. It will also help you to relish them later.
             Fry the potatoes golden brown and keep aside.
             Heat oil in a heavy bottomed pan and add bay leaves, dry red chillies, cinnamon and cumin seeds with little sugar. Let them crackle.
             Add onion and fry until it turns golden in color. Add ginger-garlic paste and fry until fragrant. Few people won’t like the idea of adding garlic. But I just love them and I’m not ready to miss any chance to use them. If you are not that of a garlic lover, skip it.
             Add turmeric powder, red chilli powder, coriander powder and cumin powder and fry for 1 minutes or until raw smell is gone. Add potatoes and make sure each piece gets coated well.
             Now add rice and give it a good stir. Remember, it shouldn’t be more than 1 min. else rice will become hard.
             Now add the fish head (or smaller pieces) and water. I prefer to do rest of the steps in microwave as after adding rice and fish things can get messy. If you feel comfortable in cooking on a gas oven for the rest process, go ahead, add salt and keep the flame on simmer and leave the pan covered for 10-15 mins or until rice is done. Do peep time to time to avoid over cooking. If you find excess water in your pan, remove the lid and keep the pan on high flame to evaporate excess water.
             But if you feel like me, use microwave. For that, add the masala and potatoes in a large microwave-safe pot along with the oil. Don’t discard the oil from the masala. Then make a layer of rice. And then top it with fish pieces and sprinkle salt. Now add water and stir in a light hand. Don’t over mix it. Don’t forget to check the seasoning.
             Now set microwave mode for 15 mins on high (900W) while keeping the bowl uncovered and wait another 5-8 mins in standby with covered bowl.
             Now you are free to sit back and relax for at least 20 minutes. Or you can start cleaning your kitchen desk and all messy stuffs. Though I can assure you will be completely distracted by the lovely smell of ‘gobindo bhog’. But still you can pretend to continue as working: P
             Once your ‘Muri Ghonto’ is ready sprinkle the garam masala and top it with 1 tbsp ghee and serve it with rice/roti or as a main dish itself along with crispy fried fish.



    </string>
</resources>